Guide to the James T. Sears Papers, 1918-2011 and undated, bulk 1950-2004 RL.01162
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1958-2004 and undated, 40 boxes
  - Audiocassette Recordings, 1971-2004 and undated
    - Professional Papers Series Recordings
      - Teaching materials audiocassettes
        - Harris, Rachel, Nerves, undated (Box 6)
        - Wayburn, Jessie and Brinkley Stone, undated (Box 6)
        - Lloyd, Cenna, Lover, undated (Box 6)
        - Bull, Lauren, Cook and Carpenter, undated (Box 6)
        - Stanley, Miriam, Era I, The Western Shore, undated (Box 6)
        - Wales, Orlando (Box 6)
        - Sears, interview of, To the Best of Our Knowledge, NPR/WPR, 1998 Feb. 7 (Box 6)
        - PI 899
          - 1997 Fall (Box 6)
          - 2002 Sept.-Oct., 7 tapes (Box 7)
        - EDLP 829, Sears, 2000 Mar. (Box 7)
        - 825, Sears class lecture, 2000 Oct., 2 cassettes (Box 7)
        - Sears lecture, 2001 Jan. 20 (Box 7)
        - Sexual Orientation Talk, 2002 Nov. 21 (Box 7)
        - Sears interview, St. Louis radio station, 1997 Oct. 24 (Box 7)
        - Sears interview, This Way Out, 2001 Sept. 30 (Box 7)
        - Tape 1, 2002 Sept. 10 (Box 7)
        - AAPP Scholars, How to Prepare to Write Your Dissertation, 1998 Oct. 8 (Box 7)
        - Institutional Climate, Journal of Homosexuality, 1995, 4 cassettes (Box 7)
        - Unmarked (Box 7)
      - Pedagogical work audiocassettes, 1983 and undated, 13 audiocassettes (Box 7)
      - Class on religious right, undated, 41 audiocassettes (Box 7-9)
      - Class on religious right, master audiocassettes, 23 audiocassettes (Box 9)
    - Research and Writings Series Audiocassettes, 1971-2002
      Titles arranged in chronological order as in main collection.
      - Major Works
        - Growing up Gay in the South, 1986 July-1988 Sept.
          - Interviews, 58 audiocassettes (Box 9-11)
            Arranged by codes given to each interviewee.
        - Rebels, Rubyfruit and Rhinestones: Queering Space in the Stonewall South, 1983 Apr.-2002 Nov.
          - Interviews, 208 audiocassettes (Box 11-18)
            Arranged alphabetically. Three recordings dated after publication of book; possibly may not belong to series.
          - Gay and lesbian Richmond [Virginia] history, 1987 Oct.-1991 Mar., 21 audiocassettes (Box 11-18)
            Arranged chronologically.
          - Kentucky activism, 1982-1983, (10 audiocassettes) (Box 11-18)
            Contains tapes of Spiral Meetings.
        - Behind the Mask of the Mattachine, 1975-2004
          Significant amounts of other related audiovisual material can be found in the Videocassettes and Audio Tapes Subseries.
          - Hal Call interviews, 28 audiocassettes (Box 18-19)
          - Other interviews, 26 audiocassettes (Box 18-19)
        - John and Edwin, 1996 and undated
          Two recordings of interviews conducted by Sears, one labeled "John," one unlabeled. Other audiovisual material, chiefly on Carson McCullers and one additional interview, are housed in the Research and Writings Series, John and Edwin Subseries.
          - Two cassettes, 1996 and undated (Box 19)
      - Other Publications
        - A Dangerous Knowing: Sexuality, Pedagogy and Popular Culture, 1989 July-1995 Aug., 39 audiocassettes (Box 19-20)
          Arranged alphabetically. Focus on the chapter about case studies in the Philippines. Contains interviews and recordings of symposia.
        - Museums, Friends, and Lovers in the New South: Laura's Web, 1909-1931, 1971 Oct.-1997 May (Box 10-22)
          - Interviews, 45 audiocassettes (Box 10-22)
            Arranged alphabetically. Contains interviews of Bragg by Gene Wadell and others.
        - Out of Harmony on the Cherokee Boundary, 1992 May-1997 May (Box 22)
          Arranged alphabetically. Part of the studies Sears conducted on sex education in different communities in the U.S.
          - Interviews, 21 audiocassettes (Box 22)
      - Research Files Audiocassettes
        - Early Gay History (Box 22-23)
          - Julian Hayes, 5 audiocassettes (Box 22-23)
          - Perry Schwartz, 13 audiocassettes (Box 22-23)
        - Florida LGBT interviews, 1995-2000, 34 audiocassettes (Box 23-24)
          Interviews used for Rebels, Rubyfruit, and Rhinestones and Lonely Hunters. Interviewees include Julia Penelope, Flo Fleishman, Paul Wegman, Merril Mushroom, Bill Pinyon (founder of Badpuppy), Bob Basker, Jack Campbell, Jesse Monteagudo, and Bob Kunst. Also has material from original broadcasts related to Anita Bryant and the Miami Referendum (1977-1978).
        - Sex Education Community Studies field research, 1990-1992 and undated, 50 audiocassettes (Box 24-26)
          Contains recordings of interviews with individuals from three communities: Chicago, Illinois, Winnetka, Illinois, and South Carolina. Most are labeled with the name and the school of the interviewee. There are some tapes that are unlabeled and undated.
      - Various recordings, 1988-1998, 63 audiocassettes (Box 26-27)
        Possibly related to three works, Combating Heterosexuality, Lonely Hunters, and Sexuality and the Curriculum. Difficult to distinguish the writing to which each individual tape belongs. There also appear to be some lectures by Sears, and interviews with him. A few are labeled as recordings of "L/G symposiums." Finally, there are four unidentified cassettes that may be recordings of meeting and publicity events (1999, 2001), and several unlabeled microcassettes.
  - Audiotape Recordings, 1958-1964, 1970-1975
    Includes significant reel-to-reel recordings from some of the earliest publicly broadcast forums on American homosexuality, with participants such as Hal Call, Del Martin, Jack Nichols, and other early activists, as well as doctors, psychologists, criminologists, journalists, and writers. Arranged chronologically.
    [RESTRICTIONS: Originals are CLOSED to use. Master copies on CD-R for all recordings are available in Box 39, from which staff can make listening copies for research access. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
    - AT-OR-1: 1958, Nov. 24, "The Homosexual in Our Society": a panel discussion in two parts, broadcast over radio station KPFA, Berkeley, California, on November 24, 1958. (Box 28)
      Panel 1: Elsa Knight Thompson, Moderator; Blanche M. Baker, Psychiatrist; Mrs. Leah Gailey, Housewife; Harold L. Call, Editor, Mattachine Review. [TRT 56:00] Panel 2: Elsa Knight Thompson, Moderator; Dr. Karl Bowman, M.D., Psychiatrist; Dr. Frank Beach, Jr., Professor of Psychology, University of California; David Wilson, Department of Criminology, University of California; Morris Lowenthal, Attorney [TRT 60:00]
    - AT-OR-2: 1959, Sept. 5, "The Psychological Aspects of Sexual Deviation" with Dr. Leo V. Tepley, Denver Psychiatrist: Luncheon Meeting, Sixth Annual Convention, Denver, Colorado (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-3: 1959, Sep. 6, "New Frontiers in Acceptance of the Homophile"; Miss Del Martin, San Francisco, President, Daughters of Bilitis, Incorporated; James Kepner, Jr., Los Angeles, Chairman, One Inc., editor, One Institute Quarterly on Homophile Studies; Harold L. Call, Editor, Mattachine Review; Sixth Annual Convention, Mattachine Society Inc., Denver, Colorado, September 6, 1959 (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-4: 1961, Sept. 2, Panel discussion on employment and rehabilitation for offenders and veterans, with Joseph R. Rowan, Mrs. Lillian Stodick, Robert Gilbert, Jan Marinissen, Charles Ives (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-5: 1959, Dec. 5, "Pornography and the Law" (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-6: 1962, July 9 and 1961, Sept. 11, "Doctor's news conference: medicine, law, and the homosexual," broadcast on KQED, July 9, 1962; "The Rejected," broadcast on KQED, Sept. 11, 1961 (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-7: 1962, Aug. 25, Conference: Harold Call, Dr. Cummings, Paul Britton, Dr. Karl Bowman. Side 1: "A Decade of Progress in the Homophile Movement"; "Progress in Venereal Disease Control." Side 2: Poetry Reading, Paul Britton; Ninth Annual Awards Banquet: "Changing Attitudes Toward Homosexuality" (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-8: 1964, Jul. 21, "An Introduction to the Homophile Movement"; Harold L. Call and Donald S. Lucas; "A Breakthrough in the Conspiracy of Silence"; Harold L. Call and Donald S. Lucas. Produced by the Mattachine Society, Inc., for a classroom project at Stanford University (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-9: 1970, Sept. 15 and 1970, Sept. 29, Side 1: "Gay Liberation," broadcast over KQED-FM on Sept. 15, 1970; Hal Call: Moderator; Bob Planz: Gay Students Union, University of California-Berkeley; Charles McWade: "Gay Liberation," San Francisco; Richard Evans: Vanguard Productions, San Francisco; Keith St. Claire: Vanguard Productions, San Francisco. Side 2: "Bay Area Gay Fund," Broadcast on Sept. 29, 1970; Hal Call, Moderator; Gary Titus, Institute for Homo. Studies; Karen Wells, Institute for Homo. Studies; Ruth Sudal, Institute for Homo. Studies; David Klineberg, Gay Lib, University of California-Berkeley [7.5 IPS, quarter-track mono] (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-10: 1970, Oct. 26 and Nov. 3, Side 1: "Obscenity and Pornography," broadcast over KQED-FM. Hal Call, Moderator, John O'Niel, S.F. "Smut" Distributor, Richard Riley, former University of California student. Side 2: "Tavern Guild of San Francisco," broadcast over KQED-FM. Hal Call, Moderator; Bob Ross, Roberta Boba, and George Banda, TransGender San Francisco (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-11: 1975 June 3, Jack Nichols on men's liberation, WFSB-TV, New England Journal (Box 28)
    - AT-OR-12: 1975 July 5, Jack Nichols on men's liberation, AM Pittsburgh Show, segments 9 and 10 (Box 28)
  - Films, 1960s, 1970, 1975-1981 and undated
    Small-gauge films separated from the papers of Hal Call and Jack Nichols, early gay activists. Titles are from original labels. Arranged chronologically.
    [RESTRICTIONS: Originals are CLOSED to use. Staff must arrange for viewing copies to be made for research access. Please contact Research Services before coming to use this collection.]
    - Call Family Home Movies
      - 1970, Super 8; Fred J. Call, St. Joseph; Farm; Jamesport; Antioch; Columbia; Trenton (Box 29)
      - 1975-1980, Super 8; Gene H. Call Family Films (Box 29)
      - 1981, Super 8 family films; Sterling, Trenton, Chillicothe; Early Mom at Home; Garner 40; Dad's Funeral (Box 29)
    - Jack Nichols Family Home Movies and Unidentified Film on Gender
      - 1960s, [original hand-written titles and numbering] #1 Scotland; St. Aug; Jax Bch (Box 29)
      - 1960s, #2 Jax Bch; Rockville; Golf; N. Carolina; Indiana; Calif. (Box 29)
      - 1960s, #3 Fall; Jax bch (house); Trip west; Marineland; Tom, Clair and kids; Uncle Alec and Aunt Joe (Box 29)
      - 1960s, #4 Finlayson (Box 29)
      - Undated, Gender #8 (Box 29)
  - Videocassette Recordings, 1972-1985 and undated
    Videocassettes and some Hi-8 digital cassettes separated from other series in the main collection, from the papers of Jack Nichols and Hal Call, and Sears' own teaching materials and other series. Others were found loose. Many recordings contain interviews, while others are compilations of news and other broadcasts focused on gay history, gay rights, or sexuality and sex education; Sears used many of these for his courses. Other recordings were collected by Sears during research for his major written works. Some boxes include manuscripts explaining video content or indexes to contents. For the most part, titles are as originally given. Arranged in groups by series in main collection; within, by date. Total running time (TRT) given where possible.
    - Jack Nichols Series Videos
      - 1970, Arnold Zenker Show, Baltimore, with Lige, Jack, Randy and Peter (Box 30)
      - 1983, "Mid-Morning L.A." interview with Logan Carter (Box 30)
      - 1984, Sep. 25 and 1985, Oct. 10, "ER" CBS; Logan Carter - "Leslie"; "Fall Boy" (?); REPO Man; Half Nelson; Pat Benatar (?); Second Sense; Hollywood Jive Squad [Format: Beta. TRT 3:55:00] (Box 30)
      - 1985, Sep. 15, An Evening at La Cage Arts; An Evening at La Cage Show; La Cage in New York [Format: Beta] (Box 30)
      - Circa 1985, Home recordings with Jack Nichols, Logan Carter and other friends at home and in Beverly Hills [poor picture quality]: some talk about sexuality and gender identity, lifestyle, biographical insights (Box 30)
      - 1986, Sept. 3, Nichols, Jack, readings and songs (Box 30)
      - 1987, Tampa Christmas (Box 30)
      - 1988, Jan. 23-24 and 1987, Dec. 25, Jack - tape in LA; Frankie - tape in LA; Christmas in Tampa [Format: Beta] (Box 30)
      - 1988, 1998, Logan Carter, 5 videocassettes (Box 30)
        Some videos are unlabeled but other labels include references to La Cage; Logan's Hollywood tour; 1998 - family Christmas; evening at La Cage; night on the town; ER episode.
      - 1988, Logan Carter and Jack Nichols, Los Angeles (Box 30)
      - 1988, Logan Carter, Hollywood, 1 of 2 videocassettes (Box 30)
      - 1988, Logan Carter, Hollywood, 2 of 2 videocassettes (Box 31)
      - 1980s, Interview with Logan Carter [TRT about 00:30:00]; various news shows about La Cage Aux Folles, nightclub; interviews with female impersonators "Gipsy," and impersonators of female celebrities [TRT about 00:30:00]; home recording of Logan Carter, Jack Nichols, and friends at home and visiting California sights [poor picture quality] (Box 31)
      - 1993, Eric Clarke Rhein, 101 Salamanders, Penn State (from Shelbi Rhein; see her letter in same box describing video background; and see related Rhein video below, in same box) (Box 31)
      - 1993, Jamie Rhein and Steve Murray Wedding (from Shelbi Rhein; see her letter in same box describing video background) (Box 31)
      - 1994, May, Maine Brimfield (Box 31)
      - 1994, Apr. 24, Salute to Larry, with Randy Wicker [TRT 50:00] (Box 31)
      - 1995, Gay Pride '95; Coco's Birthday Party (Box 31)
      - 1995, Out In New England, Gay Pride '95 (Box 31)
      - 1995, July 31, [Network Q?] [TRT 33:00]; Ashok Kave - India's First Gay Activist [TRT 27:00] (Box 31)
      - 1996, Mar. 29, Stonewall Vets Forum; Gay Community Center (Box 31)
      - 1997, Nov. 1, "50 Years of Freedom" GALA - Americans United for Separation of Church and State [TRT 1:53:30] (Box 31)
      - 1997, Sep. 14, Cloning Diana - Central Park; Clone Right!; United Front distributes badges until Central Park Police give summons and seize materials [TRT 12:00:00] (Box 31)
      - 1998, Feb. 12, Randy Wicker- Congressional Hearing; Cloning; Brad Pitt in "The Favor" (Box 31)
      - 1998, July, BBC - Cloning Documentary [TRT 20:00]; Nightline on Cloning [TRT 21:00]; CBS Morning News (Box 31)
      - 1999, Nov.-Dec., Shelbi Rhein presentation; AIDS Awareness Week - Rondout Valley High School; Eric Rhein's Life and Art (see also related videos above, in same box) (Box 31)
      - 2002, Feb. 13 and 4, Randy Wicker: Human Cloning: An Investigative Report - AE and FOX (Box 32)
      - 2002, Apr. 10-Dec. 29, Wicker, Randy debates Catholic League before Bush speech; George Bush outlines position on cloning; Wicker and Catholic League continue debate; CNN; MSNBC; Alan Keyes Show; McConnel; Wolf Blitzer on cloning Ted Williams; ESPN debate on cloning Ted Williams (Box 32)
      - 2004, The Heterosexuals (Box 32)
        Attached note explains this as a "mockumentary" inspired by a documentary titled "The Homosexuals," and created by students at American University taking a course in gay/lesbian documentaries.
      - Undated, "A Time for AIDS;" "And the Band Played On" (Box 32)
      - Undated, Logan Carter in "Gender," "Second Service," "E.R.," "Hollywood Vice Squad," "Repo Man," "Mid-Morning L.A.," and "San Fernando Valley" (Box 32)
      - Undated, Logan Carter for Ed Parker [TV broadcast tape] [format: Scotch 3M Umatic UCA20S] (Box 32)
      - Undated, Logan Carter on "Mid-Morning L.A." (Box 32)
      - Undated, Logan Carter - pictures from photo albums (Box 32)
      - Undated, An Evening at La Cage [Format: Beta] (Box 32)
      - Undated, Falling in Love Again; Do Your Boys Hang Low ("possible stuff for your column"?) (Box 32)
      - 1985, The Female Impersonator Pageant [TRT 74:00] (Box 33)
      - Undated, Logan Carter in "Hollywood Vice Squad" starring Logan Carter in his last appearance on film (2 videos) (Box 33)
      - Undated, "Hollywood Vice Squad" (Box 33)
      - Undated, "I Sing the Body Electric" Finale in FAME; Islam; Tour of Washington, D.C. (Box 33)
      - Undated, "Evening at La Cage" TV Clips, Toronto - inscribed from Danny Windsor to Logan Carter (Box 33)
      - Undated, "La Cage Aux Folles" TV Clips - John Caryle [sic] [Format: Beta] (Box 33)
      - Undated, Logan and Jack, Family Poker (Box 33)
      - Undated, Repo Man, Logan Carter (Box 33)
      - Undated, Charlie Rose; [unidentified writing] [TRT 57:00]; Organ Donation [1:39:00] (Box 33)
      - Undated, Robert Streker, "AIDS: Man-Made" (Box 33)
      - Undated, Mike Wallace, 20th Century 3rd hour (Box 33)
      - Undated, Randy Wicker on Alan Keys (Box 33)
      - Undated, Randy Wicker, "The Clone Ranger," on "The Daily Show," Comedy Channel (Box 33)
    - Teaching Materials Series Videos
      - 1993, Sears intro.; Anderson lesson on inquiry (Box 33)
      - 1994, EDLP 825 (Box 34)
      - 1998, Dr. Jim Sears presentation; Education for Diversity; EDUC 632; EDFN 845 (Box 34)
      - 1994 Aug. 1, EDLP 825 Curriculum Theory (Box 34)
      - Undated, EDLP 825 #1 (Box 29)
    - Research and Writings by Sears Videos
      - Lonely Hunters
        - Circa 1997, Lonely Hunters publicity (Box 34)
      - Behind the Mask of the Mattachine Society/Hal Call Papers videos
        - 1972-1978, Gay parades, narration by Hal Call and Ray Broshears (Box 34)
        - 1973-1977, Gay parade - gay events (Box 34)
        - 1980, Feb. 13, "A Homosexual Perspective" by Hal Call (Box 34)
        - 1983, Feb. 2, Hal Call interview: "Before Stonewall" (Box 34)
        - 1983, Sept. 27, Hal Call: "History of the Mattachine Valencia Rose" lecture (Box 34)
        - 1984, Sept. 16, Hal Call: AIDS announcements, master copy (Box 34)
        - 1986, Mar. 7, Hal Call, Phyllis Lyon, and Del Martin (Box 34)
        - 1989, Hal Call and Kevin Gladstone on "Straight Talk" (Box 34)
        - 1989, June 20, Hal Call and panel: "San Francisco and the Mattachine Society in the 60s and 70s" (Box 34)
        - 1989, June 28, Hal Call and Eric Marcus Interview: Harper and Row (Box 34)
        - 1989 May 18, Hal Call, interview with Michael O'Loughlin, San Francisco Examiner (Box 35)
        - 1991 Nov. 1, Hal Call, interview with Robert Rope, SFSC (Box 35)
        - 1994 Mar. 12, Hal Call, interview with Bert Wylen, American Public Radio (Box 35)
        - 1990, Aug. 5 and 1991, Jan., Hal Call and Paul Hardman; Ted Milunna, Call's doctorate (Box 35)
        - 1992, Dec. 14, Hal Call Interviews (Box 35)
        - 1992-1993, Dec. 14, The Hal Call Story; Hal Call interview (Box 35)
        - Undated, Hal Call and Kevin Gladstone; Straight Talk [TRT 13:00] (Box 35)
        - Undated, CBS Homo 66 with Hal (Box 35)
        - Interviews, lectures, and other events (found in Mattachine Papers Series), 1988 July-1998 Apr., 13 hi-8 videocassettes (Box 35)
          Many of these feature Hal Call; may focus on historical events or trends in gay history ("60s and 70s gay scene")
      - John and Edwin Videos
        - Undated, Raw interview footage relating to Carson McCullers' life and work, with Horton Foote, Simon Callow, Edward Albee, Carlos Dewey(?), Virginia Spencer Carr, Jordan Massee, and Sarah Shulman (Box 35)
      - Interviews on Video
        - 1993-1994, Short Mountain video edits (Box 36)
        - 1993-1994, Short Mountain interviews, Fall 1993; SMS Dubs, unedited interviews by Russell Morgan (Box 36)
        - 1993-1995, Short Mountain Sanctuary interviews, with Sylvan, Jombi, Project X and Jan, interviews by Russell Morgan (duplicate?) (Box 36)
        - 1993-1995, Short Mountain Sanctuary interviews, with Sylvan, Jombi, Project X and Jan, interviews by Russell Morgan (duplicate?) (Box 36)
        - 1995, Short Mountain unedited interviews by Russell Morgan (Box 36)
        - 1993, Dr. Carper, Dr. Hal French (Constitution and Religion in the Public Schools), Howell, Pastor Bob Shearer, and Vaughn (2), 6 videocassettes (Box 36)
    - Speeches and Possible Teaching Material
      - 1981, Nov. 2-1982, Sept. 28, "Hour Magazine" - Kinsey Report: (Box 36)
        11/16/81, news coverage of anti-gay events in Houston; 1981 mayoral race; news reports on the Austin Housing Ordinance vote, 1/16/82; news coverage of gay instructors at HPD; "Bisexual Living" - NBC TODAY show, 5/17/82; news coverage of National Gay Leadership Conference in Dallas, 8/82; news coverage of repeal of the Texas sodomy statute, 8/82; "Gays on TV" - Hour Magazine with Newton Dieter, 9/28/82; Miss Gay America - TOMORROW Show, 11/2/81; Houston Gay Pride Parade, 1981
      - 1996 Oct. 7, UW-River Falls, Sharing Separate Struggles: Racism, Sexism, Homophobia ("original tape"), [TRT: 00:00:90] (Box 36)
      - 1996 Oct. 7, UW-River Falls, Sharing Separate Struggles: Racism, Sexism, Homophobia ("tape 2"), [TRT: 00:00:90] (Box 36)
      - 1997 Sept. 26, This is America with Dennis Wholey, Show #307 (James Sears is guest with others) (Box 36)
      - 1997 Oct. 2, Jim Sears speech (Box 37)
      - 1998 Feb. 5, James T. Sears, Visiting Minority Scholar, Rethinking Homosexuality in Cultural Contexts (Box 37)
      - 2002, Gay rights rally, Columbia S.C. (Box 37)
      - 2003, Mar. 26, James Sears, Homophobia, Heterosexism, and Heteronormativity [TRT 00:32:19] (Box 37)
      - Undated, Dr. Charles Dunn, Religion on Center Stage: Political Theatre in the 90s (Box 37)
    - Various Video Recordings
      A variety of videos received as a separate group in the Sears collection. Arranged in order as originally received.
      - 1986 and other dates, Hampsters, Shelbianna, Penny, Demo 10/3/86, Sagan, Kalb, B. E. King, Sex Ed.- Donahue, Summit, Contras, Pearl, Summit Report: Gorbachev (Box 38)
      - 1980s, Gender (Logan Carter), Broward (Ft. Lauderdale) Gay Archives (Box 38)
      - 1972, Baltimore, Zenker (?), Lige and Jack, Randy and Peter and Coco (?) (Box 38)
      - 1971, Gay Pride (0-1800), other undentified names or events on label (Box 38)
      - 1969, Outrage (Box 38)
      - Undated, Bob Basker [president Mattachine Society-Midwest] interview (?), 3 video cassettes (Box 38)
      - Undated, Stonewall, Logan, Ads, Miss P. [Oklahoma?] (Box 38)
      - 1984, Guthrie Long campaign; TV commentary; Reflections in Paris (Box 38)
      - 1989, Prisms original tape (Box 38)
      - 1991, Reflections with Davie, from WSMU-TV, Nashville (Box 38)
      - 1993 Feb. 8, Dr. Sante` presentation, Omni Hotel (Box 38)
      - 1994, Aug. 1, Zamora Way (part 2); Jamie Bailey; news broadcasts of Pedro Zamora's memorial services (Box 38)
      - 2002 Feb. 26, The Writer's Circle of South Carolina: interview with Louise Andersen Allen, author of A Bluestocking in Charleston: The Life and Career of Laura Bragg [TRT 00:25:15] (Box 38)
      - 2004, Gay Pioneers, produced by Equality Forum and WHYY [TRT: 00:30:00] (Box 38)
      - Circa 1995, Oprah Show with Wanda and Brenda Henson from Mississippi, Ovett, Mississippi townspeople, and James Sears [at 28:30 until end], about homophobia in Mississippi, conflicts over Camp Sister Spirit, an intentional lesbian community founded in 1993 [TRT: 00:40:15] (Box 38)
      - Undated, Adonis excerpts (Box 38)
      - Undated, Alternative march [0-9:17]; Dancer [10:20]; Hay begins (?): Irish (?) [26:86]; Laura (?) John [28:00]; Father [33:40]; Radiant Fairies [39:20] (Box 38)
      - Undated, Dent: Why Johnny Can't Tell Right from Wrong (Box 38)
      - Undated, Sears, Jim: Gabby's Wedding (Box 38)